<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Isaac Bythewood</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/feeds/Pinry.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://isaacbythewood.com/</id><updated>2013-03-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Pinry has moved!</title><link href="http://isaacbythewood.com/2013/03/04/pinry-has-moved/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-03-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Isaac Bythewood</name></author><id>tag:isaacbythewood.com,2013-03-04:2013/03/04/pinry-has-moved/</id><summary type="html">&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://bitbucket.org/pinry/pinry"&gt;Pinry on BitBucket (Primary)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://github.com/pinry/pinry"&gt;Pinry on GitHub (Mirror)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would like to give a huge thank you to everyone for your support of Pinry and
Pinry will continue to grow because of it. Pinry's official v1.0.0 release is
coming soon/already out with many more features to come. Our current goal is a
hosted service for Pinry so that you don't have to setup Pinry on your own
server making it incredibly easy to get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never plan to forget that Pinry was built as an open platform, our hosted
setup may contain a few more features as the simple benefit of us hosting it but
the core of Pinry will always remain open-source, free, and continuously updated
because it's exactly what I use in Pinry's hosted environment. There will be
many great import and export features too so that if someone decides they want
to move between the platforms it's easy and simple to do. The Pinry Hosted will
cost a fee but it will be as close to "pay for what you use" as possible, I'm
not trying to get rich off Pinry I just want to provide a great product, however
I also don't want it to be a drain on my savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're interested in finding out more I'll be releasing http://getpinry.com/
in the coming weeks so please check there for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, thank you everyone for your support!&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>